

# Filip Stawicki

CONTACT

Phone: 507-483-701

Email: stawicki.filip1@gmail.com Ability to work: After 1 month

(period of notice)

**PERSONAL DATA** 

Name and Surname: Filip Stawicki

Date of birth: 18.10.1998 Address: ul. Poznańska 227; Ożarów Mazowiecki 05-850

# **ABOUT ME**

I graduated from engineering studies in Computer Science at the Faculty of Applied Informatics and Mathematics at the Warsaw University of Life Sciences. Currently, I am continuing my studies in order to earn a master's degree. I have been working as an IT specialist for 3 years. My professional goal is to work as a Front-end Developer. I am interested in React, in which I am constantly improving.

# **SKILLS**

#### HARD:

- Good knowledge of HTML, CSS, JAVSCRIPT, REACT;
- Knowledge of the GIT version control system;
- Knowledge of the English language (advanced level);
- Driving license. B.

## SOFT:

- Analytical thinking;
- Task-oriented;
- Good manners;
- Adapting to a changing environment.

## **EXPERIENCE**

01.01.2021 - in progress

**CIRF** 

Position: IT specialist Examples of duties:

- IT network administration;
- Administration of Active Directory services;
- Creating servers' backups,
- Helpdesk assistance to end users;
- Managing computer equipment in the unit and placing IT orders;
- Granting permissions to local applications.

01.04.2019 - 01.01.2021

Tax Administration Chamber in Warsaw Position: Junior IT specialist, IT specialist Examples of duties:

- Administration of Active Directory services;
- Helpdesk assistance to end users;
- Managing computer equipment in the unit and placing IT orders;
- Granting permissions to local applications.

01.10.2018 - 31.10.2018

Telit Management Position: Researcher Examples of duties:

- Active candidate search, preparation of candidate profiles and building a database of candidates;
- Conducting telephone interviews with candidates.

## **EDUCATION**

2021 - in progress
Warsaw University of Life Sciences
Computer Science
Masters

2017 - 2021

**Warsaw University of Life Sciences** 

Computer Science
Obtained title: Engineer